The following changes since commit 95bec8afd494c7b14e7a643a382cd9424d673262:

  Initial commit (2025-09-09 20:43:24 +0200)

are available in the Git repository at:

  . improvements

for you to fetch changes up to 3fd62471f5ff209e6052e03c92defcfbd4c3a618:

  Style: set brand color to red (#dc2626); make brand buttons white text with hover; enlarge header logo to 104px (84px on small screens) (2025-09-09 22:58:09 +0200)

----------------------------------------------------------------
Zbigniew (20):
      Improvements: fix HTML issues, add OPIS, align assets + SEO placeholders
      Replace old logo with neutral bolt SVG and update references
      Revert logo changes: restore logo01.png and references
      Hero: add background image to .hero-wrap with gradient overlay; make .hero background transparent
      Revert "Hero: add background image to .hero-wrap with gradient overlay; make .hero background transparent"
      Hero: use assets/background01.png as background with subtle dark overlay
      Header/hero tweaks: remove hero logo, enlarge brandAvatar with slight overlap; adjust grid to single column on desktop
      Brand: enlarge header logo to 120px, add white border and larger overlap; responsive downsize on small screens; adjust hero padding
      Revert "Brand: enlarge header logo to 120px, add white border and larger overlap; responsive downsize on small screens; adjust hero padding"
      Revert "Revert "Brand: enlarge header logo to 120px, add white border and larger overlap; responsive downsize on small screens; adjust hero padding""
      Revert "Brand: enlarge header logo to 120px, add white border and larger overlap; responsive downsize on small screens; adjust hero padding"
      Revert "Header/hero tweaks: remove hero logo, enlarge brandAvatar with slight overlap; adjust grid to single column on desktop"
      Hero: hide hero image and visual column; use single-column grid on desktop
      Fix PL diacritics and clean index.html; hero image removed; ensure hero background shows full image (contain) with min-height
      UX: ensure bottom sections always visible; reduce hero height with clamp and disable reveal hide by default
      Theme: align palette with background01 (dark navy bg, light text, orange brand); update header/menu/btn/card colors
      Header logo: remove white rim via clip-path and enlarge to 88px (responsive 72px on small screens)
      Build: add Jimp tool to remove white background from assets/logo01.png; processed image to transparent bg
      Revert "Build: add Jimp tool to remove white background from assets/logo01.png; processed image to transparent bg"
      Style: set brand color to red (#dc2626); make brand buttons white text with hover; enlarge header logo to 104px (84px on small screens)

 assets/background01.png | Bin 0 -> 2598558 bytes
 assets/logo01.png       | Bin 1408039 -> 577879 bytes
 index.html              |  54 ++++++++++++++-------------------
 script.js               |   3 +-
 styles.css              |  77 ++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++------------------
 5 files changed, 72 insertions(+), 62 deletions(-)
 create mode 100644 assets/background01.png
